(Raj:)Well, that's what the bullies
(Raj:)at Bruce Lee's
high school thought.
And then, bam!
(Raj:)Karate.
LEONARD: Well,
are we just gonna
(Leonard:)sit here while they do
the experiment?
(Amy:)The two of us could do it.
(Leonard:)Yeah, sure, that might be fun.
(Amy:)What's the first question?
(Raj:)Hang on.
(Penny:)Okay.
"Given the choice
of anyone in the world,
(Raj:)whom would you want
as a dinner guest?"
(Leonard:)Hmm.
(Leonard:)I can honestly say Penny.
(Amy:)Oh... then I choose a janitor.
(Amy:)'Cause I'm about to throw up.
(Leonard:)I'm in love.
(Leonard:)Let's do something else.
(Raj:)Ooh, uh, Emily
gets off work soon.
(Raj:)Why don't the four of us go out?
(Penny:)Okay.
Sounds good.
(Leonard:)Should we call
Howard and Bernadette?
(Raj:)I don't know what time
their plane gets in,
(Raj:)but let me, let me
shoot them a text.
(Amy:)Did he say anything
about the funeral?
(Raj:)Not much, but he seemed to
be in a pretty good place.
Are you kidding me?!
You lost my mother's ashes?!
No, I-I'm just saying
that sometimes